If you’re in a job performing tedious tasks, you might think that a robot could do the work instead.
如果你从事的工作需要完成大量枯燥的任务，你或许会觉得这些活完全可以交给机器人来做。
But perhaps we underestimate how much technology already helps with the activities that we would otherwise have to do.
但我们可能低估了技术已经帮我们做了许多我们不得不自己做的事情。
And as artificial intelligence progresses we might find it replaces us in the workplace altogether.
而且随着人工智能的不断发展，我们甚至可能会发现，它将会在各种场景中彻底取代人类。
For now, robotic technology is providing a helping hand for businesses, particularly in manufacturing, assisting humans in performing work more efficiently and sometimes more accurately.
目前，机器人技术正在为各类企业提供助力，尤其是在制造业领域，它能帮助人类更高效、有时甚至更精准地完成工作。
For online shopping, for example, robots have become essential in giant warehouses.
以网购为例，机器人在大型仓库里已经成了必不可少的存在。
They sort and move millions of objects of all different shapes and sizes, although humans are still needed to pick and distribute the goods.
它们负责分拣和搬运数百万件形状、大小各异的商品，不过拣选和配送货物的工作仍然需要人类来完成。
The advancement of robotics in the workplace is good for some businesses; the ones who research, develop, build and use them.
在工作场所中，机器人技术的发展对部分企业来说是利好消息，也就是那些从事机器人研发、制造和使用的企业。
The British government estimates that by 2035, artificial intelligence could add around £630bn to the UK economy.
英国政府估计，到2035年，人工智能将为英国经济贡献约6300亿英镑的产值。
But there are still tasks that robots can’t yet do, and that’s the challenge for companies such as Automata.
但仍有一些任务是机器人目前无法完成的，这也是奥托马塔这类公司面临的挑战。
Its co-founder, Suryansh Chandra, told the BBC that his technology will eliminate boring, repetitive jobs that humans don't like and aren't very good at, and also create new ones that are likely to replace them.
该公司联合创始人苏里亚尚·钱德拉在接受BBC采访时表示，他们的技术将省去那些人类不喜欢、也并不擅长的枯燥重复性工作，同时还会创造出一些很可能会取代原有岗位的新工作。
It seems inevitable that robots will eventually be able to do more and more of the jobs that are currently performed by humans, so should we be worried by the rise of the machines?
机器人最终将能承担越来越多目前由人类完成的工作，这似乎是不可避免的趋势，那么我们是否应该为机器的崛起而担忧呢？
Some experts fear hundreds of thousands of jobs could disappear as robots replace human workers.
一些专家担心，随着机器人取代人类劳动者，数十万个工作岗位可能会消失。
A report by the OECD suggests that 14% of jobs are "at high risk of automation" and 32% of jobs could be "radically transformed", with the manufacturing sector at the highest risk.
经济合作与发展组织的一份报告指出，14%的工作岗位“面临极高的自动化风险”，32%的工作岗位可能会“被彻底改变”，其中制造业面临的风险最大。
But as complete automation is some way off, for now we’ll have to work side-by-side with our robot colleagues - and manage to get along with them before they learn to kick us out of the door!
不过，全面自动化的实现还有一段距离，目前我们还得和机器人同事并肩作战——而且得在它们学会把我们扫地出门之前，努力和它们和睦相处！